Do you like stories?
你喜欢听故事吗?
I want to tell you a true story.
我想要告诉你一个真实的故事.
It happened to a friend of mine a year ago.
这是一年前发生在我的一个朋友身上的故事.
While my friend, George, was reading in bed, two thieves climbed into his kitchen.
当我的朋George治在床上看书时,两个小偷爬进了他的厨房.
After they had entered the house, they went into the dining room.
他们进到屋里后,走进了饭厅.
It was very dark, so they turned on a torch.
饭厅里很暗,于是他们打开了手电筒.
Suddenly, they heard a voice behind them.
突然他们听到身后有声音.
What's up? What's up?' someone called.
“什么事?什么事?”有人叫着.
The thieves dropped the torch and ran away as quickly as they could.
小偷扔下了手电筒,以他们最快的速度逃走了.
George heard the noise and came downstairs quickly.
乔治听到了响声,迅速地下了楼.
He turned on the light, but he couldn't see anyone.
他开了灯,但不见一个人.
The thieves had already gone.
小偷们已经逃走了.
But George's parrot, Henry, was still there.
但是George的鹦鹉Henry仍在那里.
What's up, George?' he called.
“什么事,George?”它叫着.
Nothing, Henry,' George said and smiled.
“没事,Henry.” George笑着说,
Go back to sleep.'
“接着睡觉吧.”